quiet.ly 2015-04-20

# Privacy - Quietly

## Quietly Privacy Policy

Quietly is a social publishing platform that makes it easy for you to create lists and share recommendations with anyone you want. Any registered user can create a list and include additional content like descriptions, photos, comments and links to other websites. 

This Privacy Policy describes how and when Quietly collects, uses and shares your personal information when you use our product. Quietly receives your personal information through our various websites, APIs, email notifications, applications, and widgets (the **"Services"** or **"Quietly"** ). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorize Quietly to use and disclose your personal information in Canada, the United States and any other country where Quietly operates in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We wrote this policy to help you understand what information we collect, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding your information. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@quiet.ly](mailto:info@quiet.ly). 

In this Privacy Policy, the term “personal information” or “information” refers to any information that identifies you, or by which your identity could be deduced and includes your name, email address and other personal contact information, but does not include business contact information. 

## Information Collection, Use and Disclosure

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create a new account on Quietly, we will collect your name, email address, an alias and a profile description. When you create a Quietly account by connecting via Facebook, you authorize Quietly access to some personal information stored in your Facebook account, such as your name and friends list. Of this information, your name, alias and profile description are listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing lists, do not require registration. 

**Contact Information and Address Book:** We may use your contact information to help others find your Quietly account, including through third-party services and client applications. You may choose to upload your address book so that we can help you find Quietly users you know. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. 

**Connecting from Another Service:** If you connect your Quietly account to your account on another service in order to cross-post between Quietly and that service, the other service may send us your registration or profile information on that service and other information that you authorize. This information enables cross-posting and helps us improve the Services. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional. 

**Lists, List Items, Following and other Public Information:** Our Services are primarily designed to help you create lists and share information within your Quietly network and/or the world. Our default is to make the information you provide available to your Quietly network, but we generally give you settings to make the information more or less private if you want. Your public information (i.e., name, alias and description, as well as information you authorize to be shared publicly) is broadly and instantly disseminated. When you share information or content like photos, and links via the Services, you should think carefully about what you are making public. 

**Location Information:** Your computer or mobile device can provide us with your location information. If you have not disabled these location preferences, we may use and store information about your location to provide features of our Services, such as searching for list items based on your location, and to improve and customize the Services, for example, with more relevant content like local trends, lists, and suggestions for people to follow. 

**Device Information:** We may also collect information about the device you're using Quietly on, including what type of device it is, what operating system you're using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you're using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you're using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or an Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider. 

**Links:** Quietly may keep track of how you interact with links across our Services, including our email notifications, third-party services, and client applications, by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, to provide more relevant advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on. 

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Quietly may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, some Services may not function properly if you disable cookies. 

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ( **"Log Data"** ) created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, interact with our email notifications, use your Quietly account to authenticate to a third-party website or application, or visit a third-party website that includes a Quietly button or widget. Quietly uses Log Data to provide our Services and to measure, customize, and improve them. 

**Embedded Widget Data:** We may tailor content for you based on your visits to third-party websites that integrate Quietly buttons or widgets. When these websites first load our buttons or widgets for display, we receive Log Data, including the web page you visited and your browser ( **"Embedded Widget Data"** ). 

**Third-Party Service Providers:** Quietly uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our Services such as the [Google Maps API](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). We may share your personal information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your personal information only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions. As well, such third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. You can choose to opt-out of certain third-party providers by adjusting your Quietly settings. 

**Your Consent:** We may also share or disclose your personal information with your consent, such as when you authorize a third-party web client or application to access your Quietly account. You can decline to submit personal information or withdraw your consent at any time, in which case we may not be able to provide the Services to you. 

**Law and Harm:** Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your personal information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary: (a) to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; (b) to address fraud, security or technical issues; (c) to protect Quietly's rights or property; (d) to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of, Quietly, other users or the public; and (e) otherwise as required or permitted by applicable law. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information. 

**Business Transfers:** In the event that Quietly is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. We will require in our agreement that the promises in this Privacy Policy be respected by the new entity. 

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public user profile information, public lists, the people you follow or that follow you, or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did). 

**Information Security:** We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us against unauthorized access or disclosure. 

## Accessing and Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools and user settings to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. 

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [info@quiet.ly](mailto:info@quiet.ly). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. 

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at <http://www.quiet.ly/privacy>. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an @quietlyapp tweet or e-mail to the e-mail address associated with your account or by posting on our website. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

_Last Update: October 15, 2013_

Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? Please, let us know at [info@quiet.ly](mailto:info@quiet.ly).
